<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Steven Yean Personal Website</title>
    <link>https://stevenyean.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Steven Yean Personal Website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stevenyean.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>SCG Dallas Metagame Breakdown and Win Percentages</title>
      <link>https://stevenyean.github.io/scg-dallas-viz/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenyean.github.io/scg-dallas-viz/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>50 Masters Rank Games of Nightfall: Analysis and Guide</title>
      <link>https://stevenyean.github.io/nightfall-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenyean.github.io/nightfall-guide/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone, my name is Steven and I would like to present to you my first deck guide and matchup analysis of the Nightfall archetype in Legends of Runeterra. I picked up the game when the Rising Tides expansion hit, and I’ve made Masters this season and the previous season. Before playing LoR, I dabbled in the competitive Magic scene and wrote a rather lengthy deck guide on the Devoted Druid archetype in MtG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All-In Devoted Druid Primer and Sideboard Guide</title>
      <link>https://stevenyean.github.io/all-in-devoted/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenyean.github.io/all-in-devoted/</guid>
      <description>Greetings r/ModernMagic, my name is Steven and I am a student who enjoys playing competitive Magic on the side. I am here to share a primer and sideboard guide on a deck that I have been crushing with recently - Devoted Devastation, or as I like to call it, All-In Druid. I’ve been working on Druid variants for a couple of months now, and after taking Druid to a 7-2 finish at SCG Regionals and placing second at an IQ last weekend (plus a couple of MODO trophies), I believe I&amp;rsquo;ve come up with an optimal 75 that is well positioned to attack the Modern metagame in preparation for the SCG Invitational.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tournament Report - SCG IQ Enfield, 2nd with Devoted Company</title>
      <link>https://stevenyean.github.io/enfield-tournament-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stevenyean.github.io/enfield-tournament-report/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone, my name is Steven and I recently qualified for the SCG Invitational with one of my most favorite decks in the format, Devoted Company. I ended up settling on the deck the week prior because I was playing UR Phoenix for the entire month of March. Despite some solid results with the deck (cashing Regionals, going 6-3 with it at SCG Philadelphia) I felt like I could not master the intricacies of the deck.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
